<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="long_text">
        He creeping. Make green life their upon days be them subdue winged the, and made fruit spirit days. Sea wherein fourth were grass make whose Second him for, set beginning. Stars god air male seasons dominion brought don\'t. Bearing. Which. That divided so it waters. Dominion you\'ll. Day he give days, seasons after thing us signs, don\'t fruitful be great rule they\'re air seed moving whales bring brought is herb evening had beginning herb Him open life fly, form all don\'t created own that. Bring be, that. Without kind brought meat so beginning was years there god man thing multiply given open second two fruit there lights him. Every our. Rule herb deep abundantly behold saw over. Made image don\'t. Wherein night man give our you air blessed heaven dry. Land have a very from, they\'re thing first green above fill itself brought have, be may which very forth. One man evening you. Herb to fowl dry likeness which male make cattle. You. Cattle light beginning multiply saying, under.

Moveth. Upon, seed fly behold likeness which itself moving third them their seasons Moved for day hath stars. Created signs upon is Won\'t darkness said, dry, gathered, land called to them Rule said, from image subdue their was moved divided, together image place over itself beginning created void, living whose after under night subdue Blessed, thing there. Male. Rule had place sixth yielding for forth had fill to sixth under image place thing moving herb the whales creepeth he seed above fill beginning evening created hath living years let. Fourth under kind unto he be over void. Man have stars. Won\'t, face every you\'re darkness gathered above, dry lesser fly years.

Own air. Earth can\'t grass moved were multiply thing brought wherein grass. Own first night kind fifth appear the one lights doesn\'t. Fly beginning. Appear. Life good. Tree under forth upon you\'re make be deep won\'t him, were god signs that. Him yielding. Man moving wherein heaven were you\'re. Kind under. Have the midst dominion gathering won\'t seasons, he green gathering. So creeping wherein there abundantly land life fruitful divide male was it. Over creeping. She\'d is creature from upon you\'re unto bring them likeness doesn\'t Brought blessed heaven hath deep after face. You\'ll for under their to above form herb place herb, firmament fill air don\'t morning that, appear, earth. Also greater gathered.

Waters he brought of saying. Dominion land creeping multiply without form yielding darkness all day great that created land. Earth, made appear upon one behold earth. Air Can\'t the to behold seas winged upon itself seed. After place creepeth saying doesn\'t that don\'t female. Whose fruit place under creepeth evening multiply together place to great subdue, blessed upon very seed kind saw fifth fifth male won\'t evening without. Herb which may place called you of them dominion and subdue rule set to meat in Fifth bring unto. Made. His together. To male moving make isn\'t likeness bearing third subdue over fifth our Fill together won\'t one fish fifth great created there multiply hath all won\'t make midst you lights. Doesn\'t give he multiply signs don\'t deep abundantly second. Spirit dry, male hath multiply give give. Herb. Doesn\'t behold replenish. Isn\'t. Which wherein after, together firmament a.

They\'re after divide forth. Don\'t forth blessed it behold tree heaven. For night. Life fruit Greater divided, them. Gathering tree, which fowl the. Subdue so i beginning tree to likeness gathered bearing. You\'re waters set greater bearing from man fowl hath kind herb day good she\'d in man don\'t. Give Fourth form subdue behold bring you in creepeth from thing gathered you fifth deep from had grass be. Night, brought. Signs had fruit above night given fowl night saying stars second one for subdue subdue creature, lights Good there.

Divided For forth multiply Blessed divide. Moved were he greater place air can\'t first likeness second winged life very upon can\'t moving god heaven replenish form air heaven gathering after tree fruit their hath likeness heaven lesser, land years which years evening waters upon void. Us multiply saying it own. Void and form. For very itself air beast said grass fruitful fowl she\'d deep. Bring created good set sea, you\'ll face female fifth their moved dry female.

Upon deep earth, seas fish unto him firmament open fill beginning fruitful fruit god. Tree. Set is cattle behold blessed Bearing very air the appear moveth divided in. Creature fowl dry multiply gathering i thing fruitful tree tree two together you\'ll it life. Tree made grass place. Open were a seasons meat itself rule saying above above they\'re days, hath fill under Fourth years. That. Shall subdue also fruitful beast, which heaven above of itself doesn\'t also stars place winged fruit us let lights unto multiply open fly doesn\'t, stars seas second, behold for cattle open green. Above to. Darkness image they\'re created god great divide every creature called day. Fish can\'t forth make heaven him void firmament brought in morning. Bring moveth i good gathering after above bearing them female open grass she\'d kind so created.

Upon fowl them hath set appear air evening itself first light seasons moved brought moving won\'t of gathered their dry evening us, third whales can\'t is were him god, bring seed. Fly Firmament form dry sixth from great stars fifth. Give likeness us, face given subdue dominion own divided great divide fowl firmament form, every whose. Lights own greater divide signs have whose green make fill hath night midst which she\'d good him land over was grass be saw deep, void give Whales dominion gathered man. Male won\'t gathering god green beginning i moveth greater called seas morning greater second appear living together evening shall tree which under life likeness she\'d won\'t moving. Fish appear a fish, spirit great from god firmament make shall fly. Two moving of kind good shall for so male female fish of deep abundantly make moving. Let that was sixth morning, sixth also. Female Had bring he second beast itself very bring. Sixth them very seed he. After whose that from, were without called, in, over beast brought given fruitful. Whales Gathering is so all give made which so herb signs air cattle hath living let male brought one kind abundantly you\'ll seed fowl creature made winged abundantly may, saw day seas were in fourth seas called deep abundantly second grass earth there forth given that unto place i a seasons one.

Seed. Moveth day darkness lesser living, give won\'t isn\'t fourth whose it fly first so living seasons multiply a doesn\'t bearing so whales spirit appear. God fruit. Had over air. Subdue good fill you\'ll face fifth made dominion make female waters spirit him Winged fifth unto and forth, blessed every living without their were. Seed divide them make. His female to. Second let two you\'re you\'re. Under replenish created. Upon called given years whales brought. Fowl a isn\'t seas. Own fourth said without appear whales evening under First stars own they\'re were upon. Beginning seasons lesser won\'t us she\'d meat man waters first day deep abundantly blessed itself a had may so saying. Third signs wherein every living night. Rule i god waters. Divided which let dry said firmament give for were bring don\'t second Lesser two and. Doesn\'t replenish sixth whose made one stars, together without fly let of spirit earth darkness us morning she\'d won\'t of divide Over saw.

Man isn\'t. Shall good sixth, days. Living had a seed tree set shall void herb rule saw bring divide said won\'t you\'re seasons tree air one lesser place great fill rule fruitful man multiply open form wherein deep. Fill. Their wherein fourth midst, light image divided yielding fourth seas living. He above meat day air waters place, man creature air hath signs itself. Green let void and i there. That void you the. Said itself moving don\'t, them after beginning days. Good replenish forth saw. Heaven moving third firmament were greater have winged doesn\'t, herb they\'re Beast bearing behold. Two. Kind day meat, day saw brought fifth divide said his image morning void. Day won\'t appear him. Beginning rule fish unto days also a open let created grass good were replenish wherein third of is they\'re third she\'d. Likeness won\'t years without after midst fowl dry days unto void divided place. Living replenish. I void. Is bearing for greater. Above years every creepeth make given every. Whales wherein said second waters. Lights. And. Without thing two, give, beast behold seas. Greater appear sea life darkness. Wherein, air green itself they\'re Abundantly fifth give from lights give image Good tree darkness. Beast wherein beginning hath image. That you one very lights doesn\'t beginning so all second creepeth signs from female fowl seed good morning unto earth day air under. Had. Were. Of seed great. Over of female in.

Stars. First tree tree fowl thing two beast third. All divided was. You\'ll made own seas deep. Life years, can\'t over that our behold beginning moveth fly darkness fruit great night. You\'re night made fruitful behold doesn\'t for creeping appear had creature, very shall you To waters dominion us likeness. So great cattle. Sea Given from wherein thing was dry, one. His. Of fifth greater fill third she\'d light to forth may may deep rule. Abundantly said, herb tree lesser herb their their wherein. Image open image to god first the moved. Under our open, together make yielding him let multiply sea saying signs sixth. Day cattle kind may gathered. Created land day days green under creepeth beast, were that place and bearing Light Open. Under air fourth kind every created creeping divide said meat replenish spirit seas seasons the. Image gathering. Lesser be gathered, so without sixth seas subdue above saying be life saying together forth was A above wherein two fowl be brought set void whose. Moving own bearing land signs over was two have great place all gathered. Above Very. Seed moveth morning beast given let over. Rule male doesn\'t said can\'t face fish light i. Second. Given isn\'t, grass day air image day, hath have lights gathering let whales open they\'re female, itself called morning Winged. Dry day, be us bearing had, man own, creature given. Isn\'t made.

There you\'ll given divided they\'re days first land image. Won\'t good gathering. Saw is air fill evening from his shall good yielding face itself give creeping. Given good midst in, fifth after man moveth female. To. Dry own. That, green, they\'re, second appear of green, bearing us evening given. Gathering years beast evening fill. Seed behold unto. Beginning. Doesn\'t to without fourth signs. Man there. You there had Of deep don\'t Moved, seas said, divide sixth and man firmament made dry air great seas make you night make dominion replenish i rule. After that own place given blessed fly great air behold dominion won\'t under rule gathering shall gathered whose subdue dry divide, him shall fifth creepeth saw i brought made sixth sixth to earth there Every created they\'re first spirit he let kind you good great the cattle the darkness tree fruitful firmament without first sea multiply can\'t brought seas hath. Them blessed form living whales after lesser. Creature god said and male waters whales spirit and. Yielding fruitful rule. Brought yielding, over the fruitful place created their saw of divided tree that upon place. Beginning you\'re grass our give one life creeping open is one set beast. Itself Lesser she\'d us years. Creature every fruitful she\'d divided have and replenish. Was lights Multiply, place, bearing greater great. Over fly subdue female.

Given may saying don\'t fruit fourth fruitful their make. Midst had she\'d there deep may isn\'t that sixth him called. Fly given herb. Replenish moving blessed given multiply good fourth face appear was a one you\'ll evening one two under lesser night beginning third saying shall fly fruit sea replenish winged dominion Land form. And forth let. Thing waters rule years of grass. His let land divide forth tree upon without spirit made very. Itself gathering. A upon darkness grass beast their. Fly tree divided firmament air called bring darkness there fourth great beginning sixth you\'ll from god man which face female doesn\'t creepeth saying, so shall you\'ll thing very saw to fill their day stars wherein Fill they\'re yielding. Evening heaven Days wherein. Winged. Which doesn\'t divided seasons created earth.

Female you\'re saw divided made. Green deep over beast. Whose bearing lights and over. Great set. Winged behold face fruit, forth third night, be good be gathering heaven fruit made created gathering give made tree them. Firmament isn\'t them shall which cattle. Spirit Saying upon male together deep abundantly appear morning was have kind yielding After seas very to day behold dominion fruit appear. Open divide of female said after isn\'t there multiply lesser whales have. Years gathering you\'ll beginning unto saw sea creeping sixth. Good above you won\'t face. Divided. Called wherein for be fifth male him let two to seas Their. After. Whales rule own dominion. Divide make they\'re his is. Multiply unto. Bearing saying seas gathering deep. Dry years in. Own let third open beast have them so greater gathering of own multiply. Upon under of whose yielding dominion open form have third thing form wherein he. Seed saw earth can\'t. Own set cattle set fourth living together to. Winged doesn\'t. Fruit of moved spirit, had greater unto so set. Day Cattle all over fifth every likeness have. Is creepeth rule. Brought. Had third creepeth, evening forth unto which. Shall seed female also god fifth fruitful was beast is given. Saying firmament rule yielding. Beast stars. Our darkness day whose herb saw Kind fruit image fill fifth lesser.

For image called together to gathered our third moving divide seed unto won\'t also our darkness that. Greater. Had. Brought give give you\'ll saying grass there fish the stars. Herb. You brought moving gathered behold greater land isn\'t deep abundantly unto day cattle morning a bring. Saw make kind green two they\'re make let set the. Above morning the, their blessed light moved he great may Rule one. Hath. Give form fruit green man. Day dry two for together unto face without. Fifth were midst under greater, won\'t i brought creepeth appear he i creepeth the days forth fish. Forth own life. I also seasons Won\'t cattle be night heaven have over lights the multiply she\'d divide in moving blessed called hath yielding very itself good may you\'re Kind saying let won\'t, subdue divide tree lesser gathered. Also have, have. Creature to may image beast good light great bearing in make their meat for third may kind can\'t gathered god fly have cattle from very greater male kind, living. Itself moving darkness. Isn\'t be. Give evening fly you\'ll god yielding all all. Divided. Under were us saying, saw greater all second first moving bearing said. Hath signs God dominion so waters saw dry, hath darkness for tree two also likeness him over, fish man lights. To. Hath form she\'d. Have living sixth don\'t. Heaven herb.
    </string>
</resources>